[{"id":"PSYC1","random":492932418,"question":"You're sore the next day from an intense new workout.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I must have worked hard!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I'm so out of shape.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC2","random":797898603,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC1","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1,"Dangerous":1,"Focus":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":"PSYC4"},{"answer":"What the hell was I thinking? That's insanity...","pendex":{"Safety":1,"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC3","random":49803954,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC1","answers":[{"answer":"It could still be worse.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1,"Dangerous":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":"PSYC5"},{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Safety":1,"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC4","random":466086625,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC1","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Dangerous":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":{},"linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""},{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Safety":1,"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC5","random":113714002,"question":"You walk by a homeless person and you","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Ignore him.","pendex":{"Safety":1,"Antisocial":1,"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":"PSYC6"},{"answer":"Give him spare change.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Dangerous":1,"Generous":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC6","random":469308529,"question":"The homelss person is Gandalf the Grey!","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC5","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Escapist":1,"Optimistic":1,"Dangerous":1},"achievement":"Hobo Bearer - \"You alone have beared the burden of talking to hobos. Middle-earth thanks you citizen.","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""},{"answer":"Who?","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Safety":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC7","random":277653522,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Life sucks","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Life is awesome","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC8","random":528366645,"question":"How do you feel about the lottery?","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I'M GONNA WIN","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Escapist":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"The odds are forever not in my favor","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC9","random":280473865,"question":"Good things usually happen to me.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"For the most part!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Escapist":1,"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Not really. My luck sucks.","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC10","random":662496188,"question":"You're having a hard time. Things are","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Going to get better.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Only going to get worse.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC11","random":69031842,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"There's always a chance!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I'm f***ed.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Realist":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC12","random":499297076,"question":"The girl/guy of your dreams shows up at a party you were on the fence about going to.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I knew this was a good idea.","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":"PSYC14"},{"answer":"I'm so lucky!","pendex":{"Goodluck":1,"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC13","random":568835445,"question":"She/He doesn't even notice you.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC12","answers":[{"answer":"Because I didn't introduce myself.","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Optimistic":1,"Gregarious":1,"Outgoing":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""},{"answer":"Why would she?","pendex":{"Antisocial":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Hermit":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC14","random":332617391,"question":"The party you planned literally gets rained on.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Confident":1,"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"My luck sucks.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC15","random":90199953,"question":"You've just lost 5lbs towards your targeted weight.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"My hard work is paying off!","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Optimistic":1,"Strength":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I hope I keep losing weight...","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC16","random":909561647,"question":"You see a penny while walking downtown.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC28","answers":[{"answer":"You pickup the penny.","pendex":{"Dirty":1,"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":"PSYC17"},{"answer":"You ignore the penny.","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Clean":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC17","random":695426756,"question":"The penny turns into flaming two handed sword.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC16","answers":[{"answer":"Damn I'm good!","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Strength":1,"Escapist":1},"achievement":"Lord of Pennies - \"One penny flaming two handed sword to rule them all\"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""},{"answer":"You drop it because you think it will burn you.","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC18","random":936558852,"question":"You get honked at in traffic.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"They must be having a bad day.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Sophisticated":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"YOU SON OF A B****. I'LL KILL YOU! AND YOUR FAMILY!","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Uncultured":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC19","random":204205315,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Expect the best","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Expect the worst","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC20","random":543971646,"question":"Do you find it easy to relax?","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Yes","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"No","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC21","random":554664806,"question":"Something will go wrong","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Nope! I got this :)","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Yeah...that's me.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC22","random":150971516,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Loud ","pendex":{"Social":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Quiet","pendex":{"Antisocial":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC23","random":217242322,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Dream","pendex":{"Escapist":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Real","pendex":{"Realist":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC24","random":179885604,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Finger painting","pendex":{"Informal":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Paint brush painting","pendex":{"Formal":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC25","random":294389830,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Hey","pendex":{"Informal":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Hello","pendex":{"Formal":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC26","random":125102509,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Half Full","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Half Empty","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC27","random":863340940,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Shit happens.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I have shit luck.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC28","random":469695485,"question":"","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I'll probably find a penny today.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":"PSYC16"},{"answer":"I'll probably get hit by a car today.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC29","random":329549895,"question":"I feel like I'm on an emotional roller coaster.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC30","random":637596911,"question":"You tell me to keep a ring secret and safe.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"No problem!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I'll probably lose it.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC31","random":868478148,"question":"When it comes to talking to girls","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I walk right up to them.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I suck at it.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Antisocial":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC32","random":485476977,"question":"A person bites you while you're walking down the street.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Bite them back!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":"PSYC33"},{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1,"Realist":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC33","random":22237686,"question":"They had rabies.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC32","answers":[{"answer":"That's ok. I'm vaccinated!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"God dammit.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC34","random":82104382,"question":"They're also a zombie.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC32","answers":[{"answer":"Cut off the head!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Figures.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC35","random":779933902,"question":"Someone in traffic throws something at your car.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I feel bad for them.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"What the f*** was that? Did it hit my car?","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":"PSYC36"}]},{"id":"PSYC36","random":640189213,"question":"It was an opossum.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC35","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1,"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Nooooo my window was open!","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":"PSYC37"}]},{"id":"PSYC37","random":866733096,"question":"The opossum attacks!","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC35","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"AHHH MY FACE! Opossum hits YOU for 35 (CRITICAL) slashing damage!","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC38","random":293440149,"question":"A million dollars fall out of the sky right in front of you.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Right place right time!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC39","random":872689787,"question":"You guessed how many jellybeans were in the jar!","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I'm a good guesser!","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC40","random":927349381,"question":"You got an A on an exam!","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I'm smart!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I was prepared.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC41","random":409806960,"question":"You get a speeding ticket.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Don't have my wallet but it'll be ok!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"The one time I leave my wallet....","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC42","random":844213533,"question":"Your child gets an award at school.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I made him work hard!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Wow! He beat the odds!","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC43","random":851894728,"question":"You just lost your job and you don't have enough to pay rent.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"It'll work itself out.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"CRAP CRAP CRAP!","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC44","random":679896249,"question":"You have to go to the bathroom but you know there's no toilet paper left.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"You go ahead knowing it will work itself out.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":"PSYC45"},{"answer":"You hold it in.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC45","random":809392214,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC44","answers":[{"answer":"There's got to be a way out of this.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":"PSYC46"},{"answer":"Use paper towels.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC46","random":591251384,"question":"Continue?","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC44","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":"PSYC47"},{"answer":"Abort mission and use your underwear.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Dirty":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC47","random":258899294,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC44","answers":[{"answer":"Use the bow and arrow.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":"PSYC48"},{"answer":"Abort mission and use your underwear.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Dirty":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC48","random":338995645,"question":"You shoot the ceiling and","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC44","answers":[{"answer":"A hidden roll of toilet paper is discovered!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"Toilet Scavenger - \"You could make a working spaceship out of poptarts if you wanted to!\"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":""},{"answer":"A sandwich is discovered! I guess I am kind of hungry.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"PlotTwist","linked":"PSYC49"}]},{"id":"PSYC49","random":888831143,"question":"The sandwich infects you with Ebola.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"PSYC44","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Why didn't I just take the toilet paper...","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC50","random":931807903,"question":"Bad traffic makes you late to work.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"I wonder what all this traffic is from.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"I should've woken up earlier :(","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC51","random":458086220,"question":"You hit a deer crossing the street.","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"It was probably the deers fault.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"It was probably my fault.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"PSYC52","random":44830304,"question":"This question is","category":"Psychological","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Correct.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Incorrect.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]}]
